<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Osaka Cycling</title>
    <link>https://cycling.bchari.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Osaka Cycling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 08:37:26 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cycling.bchari.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rokko Mountain Climbing - Rock Garden</title>
      <link>https://cycling.bchari.com/posts/rokko-climbing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 08:37:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cycling.bchari.com/posts/rokko-climbing/</guid>
      <description>June is a rany season in most parts of Japan. It was a happy sunny holiday when I decided to climb &amp;ldquo;Rock Garden&amp;rdquo; in Mt. Rokko with my family. Contrary to its name, Rock Garden, climbing the route is easy and fun. Recommended for kids and families.
Climbing Route Access to Ashiyagawa Sta.: 20 min. from Osaka-Umeda by train (Hankyu Kobe line). Parking lot: There are several small parking lots around Ashiyagawa Sta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Satsukiyama Hill Climb</title>
      <link>https://cycling.bchari.com/posts/satsukiyama-hill-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 15:51:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cycling.bchari.com/posts/satsukiyama-hill-climb/</guid>
      <description>A famous hill climb cycling route in Osaka, Japan. Satsukiyama hill climb route starts from the entrance of Satsukiyama driveway. This route is 6.5km long and has an elevation gain of 448m. You can see the landscape of Mt. Rokkou and the cities under the mountain at the end of the route.
Route This time I started at Max-Value supermarket then made a circuit including Satsukiyama hill climb. The total distance was 25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Osaka Cycle Path</title>
      <link>https://cycling.bchari.com/posts/n-osaka-cycle-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 14:01:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cycling.bchari.com/posts/n-osaka-cycle-path/</guid>
      <description>If you are thinking to enjoy cycling in Osaka, Japan, There would be several choices listed below.
North Kawachi Cycle Path South Kawachi Cycle Path Naniwa Cycle Path North Osaka Cycle Path North Osaka Cycle Path begins at Osaka city hall. It reaches Expo&#39;70 Commemoriative Park.
Although people usually go from south to north, I took opposite direction.
North Osaka Cycle Path - Map Starting from Expo&#39;70 Commemoriative Park It was unclear where North Osaka Cycle Path begins.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
