<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Osaka on Osaka Cycling</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/osaka/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Osaka on Osaka Cycling</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 08:08:08 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/osaka/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>South Kawachi Cycle Line - Your Return Journey Through History and Scenery!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/s-kawachi-cycle-path-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:44:08 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/s-kawachi-cycle-path-2/</guid>
      <description>On the return trip of the South Kawachi Cycle Line, I transformed a simple ride back into a historical adventure, making delightful detours to explore the charming old townscape of Tondabayashi Jinaimachi and the majestic ancient tombs of the Furuichi Kofun Group, including Hōnda Gobyōyama Kofun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Osaka&#39;s Scenic South Kawachi Cycle Line! - Outward Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/s-kawachi-cycle-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:57:06 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/s-kawachi-cycle-path/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for an exhilarating cycling adventure in Japan? Discover the South Kawachi Cycle Line, a cycling path in Osaka Prefecture, offering a refreshing escape with picturesque riverside views!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-the-south-kawachi-cycle-line&#34;&gt;What is the South Kawachi Cycle Line?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The South Kawachi Cycle Line is one of Osaka Prefecture&amp;rsquo;s grand cycling routes, stretching a delightful 21.1 km. While Osaka boasts other popular routes like the Kitakawachi Cycle Line, Kitaosaka Cycle Line, and Naniwa Cycle Road, the South Kawachi Cycle Line offers a unique charm, particularly along its beautiful riverside sections.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Osaka Cycle Path</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/n-osaka-cycle-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 14:01:40 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/n-osaka-cycle-path/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are thinking to enjoy cycling in Osaka, Japan, There would be several choices listed below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;North Kawachi Cycle Path&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;South Kawachi Cycle Path&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Naniwa Cycle Path&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;North Osaka Cycle Path&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;North Osaka Cycle Path begins at Osaka city hall. It reaches Expo&#39;70 Commemoriative Park.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although people usually go from south to north, I took opposite direction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;north-osaka-cycle-path---map&#34;&gt;North Osaka Cycle Path - Map&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;  class=&#34;mapbox h-80 w-full my-4&#34;&#xA;  data-json=&#34;track1.json&#34;&#xA;  data-center=&#34;{ &amp;#34;lng&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;135.54&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;lat&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;34.75&amp;#34; }&#34;&#xA;  data-zoom=&#34;10.5&#34;&#xA;  data-style=&#34;&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;starting-from-expo70-commemoriative-park&#34;&gt;Starting from Expo&#39;70 Commemoriative Park&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was unclear where North Osaka Cycle Path begins. There seems to be no signboards or something that indicates the cyclie path. Since a cycle road makes a round of the park, you can start anywhere on the road. (See the red line below)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
